kusd.edu 2010-06-21

# Privacy On the Web Site - Kenosha Unified School District No. 1 - Kenosha, Wisconsin

### Kenosha Unified School District and Your Privacy

At Kenosha Unified School District we respect your right to privacy and we understand that, as a visitor to www.kusd.edu, you prefer to control your own personal information and preferences. For this reason, we may ask you to register or to provide personal information and preferences when you visit certain areas of www.kusd.edu, download free software, request information, or subscribe to Kenosha Unified School District newsletters. 

  * Kenosha Unified School District does not automatically collect any personal information unless it is voluntarily provided.
  * Kenosha Unified School District does not offer or allow the selling of any user-provided information to third parties.
  * Personal information that you post to online message boards is accessible by other message board participants.

### How Kenosha Unified School District Will Protect Your Personal Information

Kenosha Unified School District will always protect the personal information that you share with us. Kenosha Unified School District stores information internally in a controlled, secure environment.

### Cookies

A cookie is a tiny piece of information that a web site stores on your computer. When you revisit the Web site, your browser sends the information back to the site. Cookies allow Web sites to maintain information on a particular user. For example, an online bookstore might use a cookie to store the contents of your shopping cart so that you can conveniently purchase a cart full of items rather than one item at a time. Cookies can only store data that is provided by the server or generated by an explicit user action. Cookies are designed to be read only by the site that provides them, not by other sites. Most Web browsers can be configured to notify you when cookies arrive and ask your approval to accept them, or to refuse cookies outright. Most browsers can also delete cookies you may have accepted in the past.

The Kenosha Unified School District Web site currently uses cookies in the following fashion:

  * To save user preferences in message boards and other online applications.
  * To record visitor statistics such browser infomation, pages visited, time spent on the web site, and the Internet address of the referring Web site. These statisitics help us improve Web site service.

### Links

Kenosha Unified School District websites may contain links to other sites. Kenosha Unified School District assumes no responsibility for the content or the privacy policies and practices of such Web sites. Kenosha Unified School District encourages you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites; their privacy practices may differ from ours.

### E-mail Lists

Addresses from Kenosha Unified School District-sponsored e-mail lists will not be compiled, collected, used, or sold for any purpose, commercial or non-commercial, other than e-mail communication regarding the topic of the list.
